eset.com 2013-04-01

# Privacy Policy | ESET

This Privacy Policy applies to these Site(s) and not necessarily to other ESET North America (ESET) sites. When leaving any Site(s), please read the privacy policy applicable to the site you are thereafter visiting. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site(s). 

**Entering and using the Site(s) you declare your agreement with this privacy statement.**

By using these Site(s), you expressly accept and give your unambiguous consent that your Personal Information gained with registration on these Site(s), or in connection with your use of the Site(s), with respect to the Site(s), may be transferred across international borders to server locations supporting the Site(s) (including but not limited to transfers from those locations back to the country of your registration) for operating and developing the Site(s), including transfers to ESET subcontractors, agents or representatives, who perform tasks related to the Site(s) and services, or for the purposes of storing the data in the relevant databases. 

**Non-Personal Information Automatically Collected**

ESET is committed to the protection of privacy of the Site(s) visitors. Please note that ESET may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related Site information to trusted third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information. 

**Personal Information**

ESET collects Personal Information for the purposes of provision, development and personalization of the Site(s) and any other ESET sites, services and/or products, research and demographics, statistics and customer care. Specifically, ESET collects personal information for the purposes of personal communication with you in order to respond to your questions, and fulfill your requests. Such information may include, among other information, your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. These data will be used in the events you have so consented, to contact you for direct marketing purposes via mail, e-mail or phone to conduct market research, and to inform you of and get your feedback on upcoming products, services and/or promotions. If you send us product orders, service requirements or if you send any material to the Site(s), we might have to contact you in order to gain additional information necessary for processing or fulfillment of your orders and/or requirements. Your Personal Information will not be revealed to any third parties without your prior consent, unless required otherwise by legal regulations, or cases, when it is necessary for proceeding of your order, fulfilling of your request, or providing interactive customer service and ESET's products and services improvement. At the same time you are giving ESET the right to provide the information you submitted to ESET, for above purposes to the partners cooperating with ESET. 

**Personal Information Security**

Please note that while there are always risks associated with providing Personal Information, whether in person, by phone or over the Internet or any other media or terminal, and no system of technology is completely safe, "tamper" or "hacker-proof", ESET has endeavored to take appropriate measures to prevent and minimize risks of unauthorized access to, improper use and the inaccuracy of your Personal Information. For example when collecting or transferring sensitive data, e.g. cash card information, we use encrypting technology. 

**Accuracy of Collected Data**

ESET will on its own initiative, or at your request, replenish, rectify or erase any in-complete, inaccurate or outdated personal information retained by ESET in connection with the operation of the Site(s). 

**Visitors Identification**

Generally, you may use these Site(s) for information purposes without giving personal information and informing ESET who you are. But, from time to time, ESET or its third-party designees may place information on your computer to allow ESET to collect certain data. This information is commonly known as "cookies". The cookies are commonly used on many websites. Cookies are stored on your hard disc in the computer, not on the Site(s).ESET or its third-party designees will use only information, they themselves placed in cookies through the Site(s) or other ESET's web sites. 

Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at our site. By means of cookies ESET is able to further develop and improve the Site(s). 

As to the former, these types of cookies allow you to log in without having to type your log-in name each time and without having to add products to your shopping list each time in between two visits, if the transaction was not finished in previous visit. 

No personal information about you is gathered through the use of these types of cookies. In other words, cookies are identifying your computer, not you. 

If you do not wish to receive cookies, or you want to be notified when a cookie is set, you can configure your browser, if the browser allows given settings. 

If you choose to decline cookies, please, be aware, that you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site(s), nor you will be able to download certain contents and/or to take part in certain transactions on the Site(s). 

Besides, the Site(s) may use different technology, which enables to ESET to collect certain technical information, for example: your IP address, type of operational system in your computer, internet browser type and addresses of connected sites, in order to improve provided services. 

ESET may use third party scripts on our sites to optimize the effectiveness of ESET's ads appearing on other parties' sites, such as the type and/or frequency of ads, promotions, or other marketing messages the customer views. 

The information collected is not personally identifiable and is limited to the minimum information necessary to optimize effectiveness. 

Available Cookie Opt-out

  * Omniture Test and Target: <http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy/optout/tnt>

  * Google Analytics: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

To opt out from behavioral advertising by networks adhering to the Network Advertising Initiative visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Underage**

No information may be submitted to ESET via the Site(s) by persons, who are minors under their applicable local legislation. In the event you are a minor or younger than legal age in your country, you will need consent from your parent(s) or other legal guardian(s) before submitting any information to ESET via the Site(s), with the exception if such activities are allowed by applicable law of your country. 

**Modification of the Privacy Policy**

ESET reserves the right to change or modify at any time this Privacy Policy, or change, modify or deny access to the Site(s), or their content without prior notice. 

**Service Specific Terms**

ESET may have separate terms for different services (for example the Terms of Usage), in which the service specific terms and conditions might be set forth (including data protection).

ESET LLC., is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of those who entrust us with their personal information. Our employees, and all those who do business with us, trust and expect that we will protect their personal information in accordance with the promises we make. In furtherance of our commitment, ESET LLC has certified to the Safe Harbor Agreement between the United States and the European Union, with respect to personal data processed as part of our human resources and marketing activities. Accordingly, ESET LLC adheres to the Safe Harbor privacy principles and frequently asked questions, as agreed to by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission. 

#### Scope

This Safe Harbor Privacy Policy sets forth how ESET LLC., Inc. handles personal data transferred from countries in the European Economic Area (EEA) to the United States that are collected or received in managing our workforce, in conducting marketing and sales, and in customer information management activities. 

#### Definitions

The following terms are used throughout this document and defined here for clarification. 

**Agent:** "Agent" means a third party that processes personal data solely on behalf of and under the instructions of ESET LLC. 

**Personal Data:** "Personal data" means any information or set of information that identifies or can reasonably be used to identify an individual. Personal data do not include information that is encoded or anonymized, or publicly available information that has not been combined with non-public personal information. 

**Sensitive Personal Data:** "Sensitive personal data" means any personal information that reveals race, ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, or that concerns health or sex life. Information will be treated as sensitive personal data where it is received from a third party that treats and identifies it as sensitive. 

#### Privacy Principles

The following privacy principles apply to the collection, use and disclosure of personal data by ESET LLC., in conducting human resources, sales and marketing, and customer information management activities. 

**Notice:** ESET LLC., will inform individuals about the purposes for which we collect and use personal data about them, how to contact us, the types of non-agent third parties with whom we may share personal data, and any ways that individuals may limit the use and sharing of such data. This notice will be provided when individuals are first asked to provide personal data or as soon thereafter as is practicable. 

**Choice:** ESET LLC., will offer an individual the opportunity to choose (opt out) whether personal data are (a) shared with a non-agent third party or (b) used for a purpose other than that for which the data were originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. 

For sensitive personal data, ESET LLC., will give an individual an affirmative or explicit (opt in) choice if the information is to be disclosed to a third party or used for a purpose other than those for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. 

**Access:** ESET LLC., will provide individuals with reasonable access to personal data about them and they may request the correction or amendment of personal data that they demonstrate to be incorrect or incomplete. 

**Transfers to Agents:** ESET LLC., will only transfer personal data to an agent where the agent has provided assurances that the agent provides at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by these privacy principles. Where we have knowledge that an agent is using or sharing personal data in a way that is contrary to these principles, ESET LLC will take reasonable steps to prevent or stop such processing. 

**Onward Transfer:** ESET LLC., will only transfer personal data to a non-agent third party where consistent with the notice provided to the individuals who are the subject of the data and any consent that those individuals have given. 

**Information Integrity:** ESET LLC., will only use and share personal data about individuals in a way that is consistent with the purposes for which the data were collected or subsequently authorized by those individuals. To the extent necessary for those purposes, ESET LLC., will take reasonable steps to ensure that the data are accurate, complete, and current. 

**Information Security:** ESET LLC., will take reasonable precautions to protect personal data from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. 

**Enforcement:** ESET LLC., has put in place mechanisms to verify our ongoing adherence to these privacy principles. We encourage individuals covered by this Policy to raise any concerns that they have about the way that we process their personal data by contacting us at the address below, and we will do our best to resolve them. We have also agreed to participate in the dispute resolution program provided by the European Data Protection Authorities Panel. 

#### Limitation on Scope of Principles

Adherence by ESET LLC., to these privacy principles may be limited to the extent required to meet a legal, governmental, national security or public interest obligation. 

#### Changes to this Policy

This policy may be amended from time to time, consistent with the requirements of the Safe Harbor. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of this policy. For material changes to this policy, we will notify individuals by placing a notice on the following Web site: http://www.eset.com/us/privacy/

#### Privacy Policy Contact

If you have any comments or questions regarding ESET's privacy policies, please contact Mr. Chad Nelley, Privacy Officer by telephone at: **(619) 876-5424** by Fascimile at: **(619) 876-5845** ; by email at: [privacy@eset.com](mailto:privacy@eset.com); or by mail at: 

Mr. Chad Nelley  
Privacy Officer  
ESET North America  
610 W. Ash Street, Suite 1700  
San Diego, CA 92101 

Last Updated: July 3, 2012
